

Ivan Gromov

Software Engineering Student

Tampere, Finland +358406278445 · <u>ivan.grcmcv@gmail.com</u>

⇔ LinkedIn, GitHub

Technical Skills

JavaScript

React

Node.js

Bootstrap

Java

C++

Git

HTML/CSS

Android Development

Hobbies

Photography, Travel, Music

Languages

English — Full proficiency

Finnish — Limited proficiency

Russian — Native proficiency

Profile

Enthusiastic and responsible Software Engineering student with the desire to develop himself and apply the acquired knowledge in practice. An experienced and valuable team player, effectively collaborating with others while being able to work independently. A capable software developer who is attentive to details and adaptable to changing circumstances.

Education

Bachelor's Degree Programme in Software Engineering, Tampere University of Applied Sciences

August 2021 - Present

Relevant Experience

Student at Samsung IT School, Saint Petersburg

2018 - 2019

- Had experience with Android development.
- Introduced to UX/UI design.
- Made my own applications for Android.
- Experienced in teamwork on a big project.

Projects

Full-Stack Web Application, To-Do — React, Node.js, MongoDB, Docker.

GitHub link: github.com/gromov-ivan/todo-app

Web Application, Weather Forecast — JavaScript, HTML, CSS.

GitHub link: github.com/gromov-ivan/weather-app

Employment History

Hotel housekeeper, N-Clean Oy, Tampere

April 2022 — Present

A part-time job where I gained my first working experience and performed my duties responsibly and efficiently.

- Adhere to all the rules.
- · Work with clients.
- Remain flexible and punctual.